relativity.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy and Cookie Policy

* * *

KCURA RESPECTS YOUR PRIVACY AND IS COMMITTED TO PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US. THE FOLLOWING IS OUR PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH DESCRIBES WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON OUR WEBSITE, HOW WE USE IT, AND YOUR OPTIONS REGARDING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

## Information We Collect

We may collect personal identification information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to: when you visit our site, register on the site, pay for a service, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. When interacting with our website, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, company, phone number, credit card information, or other personal contact information. We do not plan to have a system to comply with Do Not Track requests at this time, unless required by applicable laws or regulations.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1\. To process payments. We may use the information that you provide about yourself when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service, such as a third-party merchant vendor.

2\. To improve customer service and effectively respond to support needs or training requests

3\. To respond to sales inquiries or general questions

4\. To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for newsletter subscriptions may be used to send you information pertaining to the newsletter for which you subscribed. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables it to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. A cookie cannot read data off of your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies may do things like allow you to navigate faster through the site, remember your preferences and passwords, and generally improve the user experience. You can turn off the ability to receive cookies by adjusting your browser settings — please note that if you do so, this may affect the functionality of the website and the information you can access through it.

kCura uses cookies to compile aggregate data about website traffic and interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and content in the future. We use third-party companies, such as Google Analytics, to assist us in understanding our site visitors.

As part of AdWords remarketing, we use the Google Analytics cookie and the DoubleClick cookie together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg4VHd0m21adYaAg9yNDxJFQTiTSdorWliAwloVbVUTgmchctwp2GJgAjNVdX5eTnvU_liK7Nw1FGvAO2MinLUps2ts4sc__SSyVF7FCU6gglVus727677iacDuZaJDGl9s2vkWKy9gmbFnJTyVHgeNeMVjqG3WCh_5C10Gqr73KbdwD0__6mf5ax3UV_6tHffg9HzX).

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746).

## Disclosure of Information

Your privacy and security are important to us. Therefore, kCura does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website or conducting our business, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Details from a credit card payment transaction may be made available to a third-party merchant per a web-based transactions management system, which allows the merchant to track transactions and process refunds. When kCura transmits sensitive information (such as a credit card numbers), we use commercially customary encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## External Links

kCura’s website provides links to other third-party websites. Even if the third party is affiliated with kCura through a business partnership or otherwise, we are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only, and you access them at your own risk.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## No Error-free Performance

KCURA DOES NOT GUARANTEE ERROR-FREE PERFORMANCE UNDER THIS PRIVACY POLICY. WE WILL USE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO COMPLY WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TAKE PROMPT CORRECTIVE ACTION IF WE LEARN OF ANY FAILURE TO COMPLY WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY. HOWEVER, YOU ARE ASSUMING ALL RISKS ASSOCIATED WITH INTERNET ACTIVITY AND E-COMMERCE BY USING OUR WEBSITE. WE ARE NOT IN A POSITION TO GUARANTY THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL NOT BE HACKED OR OTHERWISE IMPROPERLY TAKEN WITHOUT OUR KNOWLEDGE BY A CRIMINAL OR OTHER THIRD PARTY. KCURA SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES RELATING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or payment processing on the website, you may contact us.
